Akash verma

Self-motivated to be a software developer and a researcher in an IT Company to utilize my ideas, knowledge, and determination for the proliferation of the organization.

Apassionate programmer, a voracious reader, and a keen learner.

EDUCATION

Patel Group of Science and Technology, Indore, Madhya Pradesh— Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science

2022

With a CGPA of 7.90

Pink Flower Hr. Sec. School, Indore, Madhya Pradesh— 12th Grade 2018

From MP Board with 71.6%

Touchstone Public School, Bhind, Madhya Pradesh — *10th Grade* 2016

From MP Board with 75%

EXPERIENCE

Oepp Innovations Pvt Ltd Indore

Machine Learning Engineer - Intern (Nov 2019 - Jun 2021)

Tech Driven Basic Pvt Ltd Indore

Python/Django Development - Intern (Aug 2021-Sep 2021)

Canopus Infosystem Pvt Ltd Indore

Machine Learning Engineer-Intern (Sep 2021-Nov 2021)

Webkorps Optimal Services Pvt Ltd Indore

React Js Developer - (Jan 2022-Present)

PERSONAL DETAILS

DOB: 15-July-2000

Gender: Male

• Marital Status: Unmarried

Nationality: Indian

• Languages: Hindi, English

+91 9165761624 akashverma20405@gmail.com 3112 sector-E Sudhama Nagar Indore https://www.linkedin.com/in/akash-verma-2041a1179/

TECHNICAL SKILLS

C Python React Js Node js Express js

Mongodb Machine Learning and Django

Html Css Bootstrap Javascript and SQL

ACHIEVEMENTS

Hacker Rank: 1st Rank in C and 1991th Rank in Python

Microsoft: 98-381 Introduction to Python with 91% grade

Google: Google Analytics for Beginners.

Hash Code: In Feb 20th 2020 Rank 9047th Place

Kickstart: In March 22nd 2020 Rank 1041¹ Place

PROJECTS

- Search youtube content from video using React js
- Scraping AgMarket Website using Python
- Crop Price Prediction Model using Machine Learning
- Rover Detect Image Object using Machine Learning

CERTIFICATES

- Techgig Python Course
- Coursera Machine Learning
- BM Open-Source Tools for Data Science
- Udemy Deep Learning
- Google Crash Course on Python